yeah all right guys we're here with Tim
roughing one of the authors of the coin
shuffle plus-plus paper to talk about
privacy so this PowerPoint and the
presentation team will do that himself
and not a lot just sit back yeah hey if
sorry if this will look Vietnam but they
had to send my slides to to our reef to
share the screen sorry I can't click
through the slides he needs to do it
could be local to it but maybe just pop
up a few things on the slide piece maybe
like actually the the the entire slide
after we are the next thing yeah so this
is your puppet cameras but this is just
to show you a little bit how ours four
things here so we have a transaction
right and fellas on the left and she has
a key and you have maybe some pizza
dealer on the right and and again
Ellis's change address which is trust C
here and then D sub transaction as well
at the face I inserted this check mark
things basically two signature re well
and then we send a little bit car
Network and natural cycles validated and
so on so I think this is all the things
that we need to get in and also here I
mean I included all slides because I had
to anyway but I am told you to tell you
that privacy is important right and that
you have a lot of privacy issues for
example the malls on public looking at
the blockchain and yeah even worse you
cannot leak addresses to each other just
by looking at links on the blockchain
so maybe go to the next thing you had a
lot of things yeah link address to cou
you know that stuff and then you can
continue with the other tools and yours
you'll know know know that stuff when
it's huge we have that stuff
Yellin demise you for you
the DMS you for for-profit actually so
proving privacy in the air have some
picture with some privacy technology so
this is just to show you where where
quadropple stands this big picture so
yeah so actually I could basically puts
coin draw and instead here probably and
it would be another picture the basic
idea here is that with coin drawing or
coin shuffle and fun mixing and
charnival also tumble bit is the same
category we can't do so much in terms of
privacy but we are pretty compatible
with the cone because it works currently
in Bitcoin and of course if you if you
want more privacy you can have fences
here enlarged truths and Technology
expectancy Lokesh
but this will never be integrated in
VidCon I guess so yeah and then there's
some something in the middle maybe that
I can briefly mention in the end here
which is like which is when you shuffle
if you if you can have amount privacy in
Bitcoin by adding something like
potential transactions them mixing
suddenly gets better and it can have
better promise even evolution okay this
is a conjoint seminar so again you can
quickly go over the slide because I
don't need to explain you how mixing
works we do it via a multi-input
multi-output transaction that you all
know as a conjoint the interesting thing
here is if you kind of if you want to do
this transaction yeah Alice Bob and
Carol need to come up with a new list of
the freshness of output addresses C
prime a prime B Prime
in there in a way that should nobody can
can tell which one thread which of these
needs belongs to to achieve zero next
[Music]
yeah and the way we're gonna do this is
peer-to-peer mixing protocol and this
option fee maximum protocol this
controversy is what what speeds up your
mixing as just if you look at it as a
parameter it's it's a protocol we have a
number of participants and this example
if four participants they all have a
input message the message was are a
prime B prime C prime D prime and like
in our in our code next thing exam but
this would be those would be the off to
the trusses where it appear on the
right-hand side of the control
transaction and our Peter Piot mixing
gives you is his output is the thing on
the right side is basically a short list
of those input must
such that no one can tell which wizardry
loans to which user but the messages
will all be public next right and the
trust model we want to have here is
really a peer-to-peer trust moments that
there are no there's not much at rest of
the the peers don't trust each other
into some random strangers on the
internet hole should be the case third
party rattles what I mean that is we
don't rely on anything like like total
provide anonymity so in this example
here now look at the left hand side
NSF Dave could be malicious and this
means for anonymity that anonymity said
it reminds the set of honest users so
Bob and Carol still have of annuity
among each other
of course now they only have anonymity
set of two because they can't have
together with the attacker right just
possible next because exactly we have
those links here so if the attacker
controls LS then the attacker knows that
a prime is Alice's address and you take
a controlled safe then he knows that T
prime states address yeah can't provide
a little-bitty with those two addresses
but as I said like Bob and Carols
together the new media set up through in
this example with the leather property
that we want to have next to anonymity
is terminations simply means the
protocol terminates and the presence of
licious users which means that there
should be users that can stop us to can
that can stop on students from finishing
the protocol the only thing we assume
here is what I mentioned last week in
the informal discussion about
suppose already determination we assume
that there is a positive board but what
do we mean by that it's basically a
server in the middle of where we all
connect to and the server handles the
podcast for us and because we are in
this peer-to-peer trust model we don't
really trust the server for liberty but
we trusted for termination instead and
in practice as we said if the server is
malicious or just broken then the tears
won't be able to finish but nothing bad
happens they could just switch to a
different server however no matter how
this server is the server can't break
another machine so how does it work it's
based on a DC mode which is a road which
is very good sense for timing
cryptographers Network and I'm talking
for network is a Viet named for the
following actually rather simple concept
saying you have again three users now
and assume these three users have
pairwise shared keys and the keys are
the numbers on the on the triangle here
so for example Alice has a shared key
with Carol that's the number one the red
one key here and hear an enemy pair has
a chef of it in now endless on the top
she also has a message and I suggest a
bold thing she is a one bit message
which is also one now what else this is
Alice takes her message to one and adds
up
the thing in the parent is the two keys
shared with the other parties the blue
key at the red key let me get one plus
one plus one and if he if we work in the
pitch fields or basically you can think
of X or instead of plus ten results
here's just one and then Ellis will
broadcast is born and now now Bob and
Carol to the same of the Bob has a
message which is a symbol here Bob adds
T to other keys and broadcasts result
and Carol does the same and now if the
cool thing now is if we add those three
messages up the DEF CON broadcast which
is 1 plus 1 plus 0 then this basically
means that we have yeah so like if if I
expanded if just this result and now we
see that every key has been added twice
which is kind of clear because it has
been added by both sides of the of every
of those connections positive so that
means that all the keys here cancel out
and we are left with the sum of the
messages here which is 1 plus 1 plus 0
so any fee if you at all so get away get
0 and 0 is indeed some of the messages
that users had in mind so interesting
figures know that this kind of this
gives the user some form of anonymity
this very simple setting so we can now
we know what the sum of their input
messages is but we don't know what part
to this song this is this is a form of
anonymity basically but
this was kind of a very simple and or
for the song example because in in
practice we we don't want to okay I
should follow the slides in practice we
first of all if you do want to do this
in practice we need to obtain shared
symmetric keys this is not hard because
we can trust to a cryptographic key
exchange this is kind of standard can do
the VM addiction strange for example but
functionality-wise what we want to do in
practices if someone to send just
messages read messages for example
become a transistor this is also not too
hard to do now I shown you I've shown
you an example with the bit field which
is the field to just basic and viewed as
a mathematical field what we can also do
larger in tetris abuse but refer that
heels with them but most importantly if
I think what we've seen in the example
is then compute the sum of their
messages but if you want to do peer to
peer banking we don't want the sum of
the messages of the people the entire
sent right so we want the list of the
messages not a song now what what a lot
of proposals and practice to and I think
you two there two weeks ago and the
seminar here is try to use some some
slots reservation for example in this
picture here me what have these slots
because we have users
and assume there was a magic way such
that every every user gets a slot in an
anonymous way so Alice here the first
user she has the middle slot the second
slot or pass the first slot carol has
the third slot and now for example the
puppet will transmit his message and the
first slot m2 and I'll be basically what
we could do here so you could run a DC
net and every of those three slots and
next and then NS Yasim forgot to say
that Edison so independent the slots
where people don't have to sign the
satchel since heroes so if you look at
their first slot we had the zeros which
are basically just some form of padding
we could say and and pumps message then
they would have two messages but the
problem here is we could we could have
to message respect to the problem here
is that this needs this what I called
magic not assignment so in order to to
make this work we already need some
protocol that provides unanimity in some
sense and this is where most of these
proposal streets not reservation
actually fail and practice because it's
a chicken and egg problem you need it in
order to get a new materia you need and
another melindam was sub protocol this
confuse love discernment and because
this is hard those protocols in the
literature to do Revere's tricks that
mostly are not great because they can
fail in practice so for example what
they often do is that you guess or slop
randomly you say we have a thousand
slots available and then every user
guesses
random slot and this kind of works in
practice but it's pretty annoying
because now instead of running 3ds
emails we need to run without sleaziness
so we need a lot more communication and
even like with a thousand it could be
that ellison pop both selects the same
slot and then like say they all they
both select slot n then installed n we
both have not m1 or m2 but we actually
would have n1 plus n2 and this is just
not tier 2 result that we want so this
is not great what we do instead is based
on on a idea that it's pretty old
already at the picture on the after
dissonance and the idea is you go into
can I have a question so why wouldn't a
lot assignment working since everyone
knows about everyone why wouldn't the
slot assignment just be decided based on
off abetik our ordering of each other of
every bus public kids right yes but like
the problem is we we also looked appears
here want anonymity even against each
other right so like if everybody in the
shuffling knows that like if Ellis knows
that all past the first slot can't get a
little-bitty because whatever message
appears on the first law that will be
pops yes make sense thank you can I ask
one question
yeah why are finite fields needed if you
can do a DC net for one bit
can't you do it for ten bits or any
arbitrary number of bits just have
shared keys that are M bits long and
just by you mean just by using X or in
sort of fields that's right in general
you can do this with these peanuts and
this is what people usually do the
reason why I need to finite fields is
exactly on the slide I'm talking so this
[Music]
so what we what we do instead of this
slope reservation thing is actually it's
abusing a method that has been proposed
to the slop reservation but we use it to
send the messages directly so what we do
is we have something could called slots
it's not really love something like
slots but we have maybe maybe it's
easiest think of n slots here we have
end users and we have n slots but
instead of sending the message in only
in one slot and sending zeros and all
the other things
Alice does here instead is she takes her
message and one censored in the first
and now she she will send em one squared
in the second slot she will send em one
to the three in the star slot and so on
up to M 1 to the N could you explain why
she doesn't lose anonymity when she in
the first slot when she broadcasts M 1
because maybe click Next
because everybody will do the same so
also pop will send em to will defer in
the first slot and then to square and
the second stall and so on so everybody
sends the same in the same slot this
make sense
so if Bob here's M 1 nm 3 can't he know
that M 1 comes from user 1 m3 country
[Music]
yeah I think the the thing that you're
missing here instead we are still doing
it this Enid and all of those slots so
we still have to check he's they are not
in this picture because here I'm on the
slide I wrote just what the basically
what the input message is to the
decedent will be in every slot but just
as the example we've seen in the
beginning with just single bits in an
area of toss lottery we run a DC net
with the with the shared keys added so
Alice Wilma
then in the first slot not simply
broadcast a bond but she will send em 1
plus she'll keep the Bob plus red key
with Carol and so on plus red key with
with user n so only after we've we have
obtained all the old rules the first
slots of the first column here these
Keys will cancel out so just by looking
at Alice's broadcast on the network you
can tell that my nose in there does this
make sense yes so sorry follow up
questions so that doesn't m1 interfere
with m2 when the yes yes and we will
come to
maybe click Next
yes
so you said m1 will interfere with them
to here and that's kind of that's kind
of true what people have we have all
those messages in the the maybe yeah
maybe that's that's look at the first
mode of you have all the first lot all
the keys will cancel out this is still
true but still like everybody basically
sent this first also we won't get a
single message there but what we will
get is the sum of all those messages and
in the in the second slots in the second
column we will get to some of the
squares and so on up to the to the last
slot this make sense so far when we're
doing sums are we doing sums over a
finite field or exercise yesterday
learning some so violent fields I think
this is thanks for reminding me I think
this is now and not yet but like yeah we
maybe click Next sorry I'm right here
it's what you do beat those thumbs yes
and sorry I don't have slice for for
exactly the thing but well now it don't
see the slots anymore so take a leaf so
okay now we have those power sums and I
think I mean it could go into that in
detail maybe later if you're really
interested and I don't have slides for
this but I really I think it's not it's
not super important the thing is here is
that if you have this this list of the
sums here of those power songs then you
can compute the messages
again and just in information
theoretically this I mean this is not a
problem explanation but at least if you
look at the number of bits here that
make sense right we have n messages all
together because we have been users and
let's say every message has B bits so if
you have the list of the of the power
sums here we have n times P bits and n
times P bits is also the same amount of
information that we had in the initial
list of yeah if you just wrote like the
list of messages tall so this is the
same amount of information and because
we used we use a proper encoding like
this or some thing is just one encoding
of a list of messages you can decode it
back and get the messages back and forth
for this to work we need finite field of
automatic that's why we we do some some
finite fields a set of tracks for this
this wouldn't work with if you use XO
and okay now the problem in the big
problem in DC Nazis and that they can be
disrupted which basically means if there
is one malicious user let's say your
purpose malicious Bob could do is
instead of instead of sending M 2 and M
2 squared and so on and following this
nice algebraic structure that just
posted follow Bob could just sent
in every slot for example like
random values or anything else that he
had taught him wrong screw it and now
the problem is if you don't want to sum
up in the slots of course we can sum up
we get some sums but like those sums
will be again butchered and yeah even
worse because you're doing like n DS
units here or this unit and every of the
n slots up here stays fully anonymous
right because this was the core property
of the decedent that we can compute the
sum of the messages we can do this here
there is not but we don't know who
contributed so we can't tell who
contributed you just see in the
end ok we don't get any message respect
like our decoding procedure doesn't work
but then we don't know what to do so
what do we do then well next yeah in
case of disruption break anonymity and
well this may sound like a bad idea but
let me explain why this actually works
and to understand why this why this
makes sense we need to have a look at
the flowchart of the culture of the run
so the first thing we do like everybody
generates the fresh with Korn interest
this is gonna be
output in the the contra and transaction
on the right side and it won't be our
message in the peer-to-peer mixing
protocol then peers to key exchanges the
runt if you Hellman key exchange on I
don't need to explain you how it works
just it makes sure that every every
payoff users will have a shared key that
they need for the dissonant okay then we
run the actual DC net and then we would
run it in slots as I've just shown you
and then now if if we would proceed like
I like I've shown you on the on the
previous slide and actually this is not
that this is not a real this is this
will not be the final flow chart of
contra for both of us it will come to
that later but they're from you at the
moment so if we were to what we've seen
on the last slide we need to somehow we
need to check if our run has been
disrupted the problem is namely that it
could be that the run is like disrupted
for well how should I or should I say
this persuade and so like if you get the
if you get the the outputs the only
thing you can you can do now is to see
if your own message is there right like
if you if your Ellis you get those power
songs in the end or if we hope that they
are power Sam's you try to decode the
the list of messages and then you have a
candidate result for the product the
only thing you can do now
you could look at if you're all messages
there which basically means that no one
disrupted your message can you can you
instead of looking at your message
although doesn't matter that that's good
but instead of looking at your message
can you just check if we if these are
Bitcoin addresses the or you
mean again you could have some some
redundancy in there so yeah but doesn't
matter because checking if your messages
there is just as easy as as anything
else yeah let me think about this for a
moment the question if if if
can be constructed in a way that still
valid Bitcoin addresses yes yeah this
problem so a I can't the total tax is on
the size but what what could happen
instead like in the example pop first a
malicious guy right so let's say Bob
since his message is lost then basically
Bob sees all the other messages Bob
ceased all the other rows in a sense and
he sees all the other messages he sees
the list of all the the other messages
that the others won't want to send and
then he could it's it's not clear from
the slide here but and he could
construct a special form of
messages things that only disrupts for
example editors message and not the
other messages okay
no not okay because then everyone would
be able to check if Elise's message is
Bitcoin address valid Bitcoin address or
not I don't know okay so what Bob sees
is pops is just a list of the other
messages he doesn't know which message
belongs to which user so he sees somehow
that m1 is there which is Elvis's
message but he doesn't know that it
belongs to Ellis but now because he
knows m1 he could send such
that M 1 is disrupted
it's basically replaced by a random
message or a message of his choice even
and the other messages are not yes so he
could selectively disrupt messages even
though he doesn't know to which users
those messages belong they make sense
thank you so he swap he could swap
Elise's address right swapped around the
mattress to his own address and for
example yeah yeah and that's why we
would need so long
ok what I was saying before is that the
only thing L is now at the end of the
t's in that round but what she can do is
she can look at the set of messages and
see if for all messages there right but
she doesn't know if the other messages
are all there she's she would see some
messages there but she doesn't know if
for example of celts message has been
replaced or not and the important thing
at this step here is that however we all
like all the peers in the protocol needs
to agree whether disruption has happened
or not because if it has not if there
was no disruption then like this is the
case you see now on the slides and then
they will go ahead and create the
contract transaction
for assignment however if one of them
like if one was disrupted then what they
want to do is they want to reveal the
key exchange secret should basically a
sandy loam ization step basically means
that the all agree like all the peers in
the protocol agreed that we give up this
round we came up on the luma t in this
front and thanks and we discard the
addresses that we generated to the
beginning we need to give me a moment to
convince her that this is not a bad idea
why can we discard those well I mean
these are trusts so far these are just
random it coordinators is right if never
told anybody who sent those money there
and we will never do it again in the
future so it's not a problem at all to
throw those away but now because like
because given that the key exchange
secrets
everybody can compute the shared message
at the the shared key is for everybody
which means that L is now knows the
shared key step bob has only with her
she she knew that one before because
shared key but now she knows also the
shared key that Bob had with Carol the
pump and the Dave and so on so now
basically everything is public in this
in this run so everybody can just look
at everybody's messages like all the
oldest guys will now figure out that oh
actually Bob sent and didn't make sense
it didn't fit this algebraic structure
basically they look at pops pops
broadcast in this second Rowan sense and
subtract all the the shared keys that he
had with the other peers and they
like now and then they look at the
result and see the resign should be in
the first slot m2 in the second slot m2
square and so on and they just can't
shake tower ops message was follow this
this euphoric structure and yeah they
figure out that pups messages don't
follow the structure so they know Bob
will actually images they can kick them
out and start from scratch
does this make sense so far yes it's
clear for me and then and then if they
if no one signs in a particular
transaction that's pretty trivial to
find right right exactly this that's the
case now next maybe then okay is
everybody sighs okay great success but
if not we can again maybe actually that
that that that error could be wrong here
I mean in that case we don't need to
discuss addresses any better do okay but
I do but the important thing is here
like yeah if if somebody refuses to sign
here then we know that this guy is
malicious or at least offline and we can
execute him however this is not okay
this is trivial to implement them but we
actually need to be careful for this
case as well
because the protocol somehow needs to
make sure that if we reach that point
where we think that there was no
disruption then there was really no
disruption to make sure that we are
excluding the right guy here but the
protocol actually has this property so
it can't be the case that everybody
thinks that there was not an option but
actually and as this message was
disrupted so she's evil laughter we
refuse design because she would lose
money by sending it to wrong address on
the corner but everybody else will think
that she actually needs to sign the
transaction just the protocol also make
sure that this comes up yeah okay and
this is the basic idea how we provide an
annuity and termination at the same time
by basically cleverly giving up on
illuminae in in case that the protocol
is disrupted that we can to me because
then we gave up anonymity for the single
run we can figure out who's who solution
and we can you can kick him out
I'm side topic of fresh message needed
so I like what I told you now is
basically the entirety of the protocol
is this why this works with giving up on
the limit is because we have those kind
of fresh with Cohen keys right we can't
throw them away and nothing bad happens
not not for our money and not for
annuity but then everybody knows that I
wanted to use this address but I never
used it in fact so I can I can give up
anonymity for this one and this works
because we can generate the dresses and
can discard them generate new ones and
so on but what if we if we want to send
messages that are that are kind of fixed
that are not too random Bitcoin
addresses and maybe a useless protocol
beyond Bitcoin for example two
confidential documents like such as
confidential document as on the slide
here I would call this a fixed message
and it turns out that this is not
possible so if we if you look at
features of key to keep mixing prana
concept before I told you you should
provide anonymity they should provide
termination and now if he adds support
for fixed messages as a third property
and contract loss plus provides
anonymity and termination rate so if he
had support for a fixed messages next
then we can ask is there protocol in the
section of all these circles in the
middle and what this turns out you mean
hmm what this admonition mean
termination means that the protocol
terminates even if there are malicious
Pierce answered not termination would
mean if there are malicious years then
the protocol just doesn't finish or it
is important is maybe it should have
been called successfully so you can
imagine that the protocol that doesn't
provide termination basically it for
example it tries to start mixing with
the DC net and then it notices all that
what's this well fails just pods okay so
we fit aboard if it notices that there
was disruption then that would mean
termination is not not insured right
well okay yeah so I think Adam like
currently wasabi does not guarantee
termination right because if a cointreau
doesn't happen wasabi bands a coin and
then reopens the round and more
malicious people can enter the round so
but one way to make it guaranteed to
terminate is to only allow the same
participants and then exclude them so
that it converges to a smaller and
smaller number isn't the termination is
to basically being able to identify the
malicious party no no in this case I'm
saying specifically a given F malicious
peers okay can you tell me when wasabi
will do a coin join and in the case of
coin shuffle plus plus the answer is 4
plus 2 F rounds and in the case of
wasabi is just when we've banned enough
people and there are no more malicious
peers so but wait let's go back to
termination you just said that that if
if the round aborts then isn't that that
means that it aborts in a way that you
cannot figure out who was the malicious
one I think termination in this case
business that it's successful that
eventually there's a coin joint yeah I
think what you're what you're mixing up
here is
when when I say anonymity and
termination your particular termination
I look at the entire probable so like
teeth the entire protocol provides
termination and it does so I like the
inner working is that it tries to to run
once and if it sees that this run
doesn't work there are these thoughts
okay so that but like when I say
termination I look at the like the
entire protocol in the black board as a
black box doesn't matter well that for
the doesn't totally yeah very for
hanging on it but I think it's important
so does that mean it could still be
possible to provide anonymity with big
messages if successful termination of
the entire protocol is not a requirement
but what is the requirement is actually
to being able to identify the malicious
peer so maybe maybe let's finish the
slide and come come back to this
question and maybe it's answer then
maybe not and so what could be
interesting is to have a protocol in the
middle that has all those three
properties but it but it turns out this
is not possible
interestingly there was a protocol
called descent at CCS that was supposed
to be in the middle and has all the
properties but it turns out it doesn't
provide anonymity so like if you if you
he would code it exactly like it's
written the paper to provide termination
and fixed messages and this anonymity
answer your question no no my was that
if you can you can identify the
malicious peer they make that really
matter if termination happens or not of
this protocol rounds because you could
happen okay sorry go ahead
that's that was pretty much it okay
again when I say termination I don't
talk about it don't mean termination of
a protocol run of a run that that can be
aborted I mean termination of the entire
frame like the entire frame with a big
loop so okay so would them okay so if
you can identify the malicious peer but
you don't exclude it but create what you
have to create a completely new protocol
and from that you exclude it that would
mean that it is a terminating protocol
okay fine let's go okay just to clarify
coin shuffle plus plus is a circular
protocol it has four it has six rounds
total six steps and then four of them
are repeated every time someone disrupts
right yes yes and that's why I like a
look the entire thing like with the
circular ringing it provides termination
I think this is all I I wanted to say
you yeah okay and and hey I can actually
show you how this annuity attack on long
distance works and I don't need to tell
you a lot about the same but think it
cancer be instructive the only thing I
think you need to know is that like the
three points on top
dissent precedes broadcast drones the
outcome of the protocol is revealed to
all the users in the last podcast and
also a network attacker sees the outcome
of the proper code of the last podcast
outcome so to remind you what is the
output of a or the outcome over into P
mixing protocols just a list of messages
now let's say we have Alice Bob and
Carol and they all have their their
fixed messengers their documents and
opposite honest guy here and we are the
network attacker now what we do is we we
listen we just let the users run the
protocol we listen to the to the
messages presently as natural attacker
and we only interfere with it in the in
the last broadcast of the of the first
run so what we do is the block we talk
pops message because your network
attacker we can we can do this but if
you see it you just don't forward it to
the others which means that he has a
method of attacking we learn the list of
messages that people wanted to send
these are the three documents here on
the right hand side this is the the
right hand side here and on the
slightest an eft attacker so here we see
what's going on we see the list of
messages but we don't know yet which
message belongs to which user but okay
now we brought Bob so now what happens
is because you've blocked Bob's last
messages and the proper call is supposed
to provide termination the other
remaining part is like hey listen Carol
they need to somehow start from scratch
right and they to a second run of the
protocol and now because Bob is not in
the protocol anymore taking
I'm out because he appeared to be
malicious to the other two parties
Pop's message won't be there in the
second run so and now it but the
attacker can do is he just looks at the
font come off the first one and the
second trial in compare stop and he will
just notice that the missing protocol
the missing message is the two gray one
with the confidential mark on it we can
see announced that he blocked off he
knows that this is the message from Bob
this makes sense probably okay a few
feet over to ask sorry I was just
blanking out it so how is it that you
can figure out okay there are multiple
things here so yes I didn't explain you
how descent works and works differently
from from what I see nuts so basically
it's a little bit like or it's it's
pretty similar to the contract the one
that you also discussed but my point I
understand it it doesn't really matter
right so it detected a that I show here
what equally be true if we if we would
try to run if you would try to use fixed
messages in control itself going to be
exactly the same issues really how the
protocol looks like
but in the end of the proper call at
some point you need to review the
messages right so what do you take er
here does is in the first run it like it
just looks at at the protocol passively
until the last translate basically he
observes all the messages of all the
people that then she just he just sees
the outcome of the protocol which is the
list of messages and the father there's
nothing wrong with it because he it
doesn't learn which message belongs to
be chosen this might mean a dumb
question but how practical is it to
block someone from from the protocol
made protocol I think this really
depends on the on the net on the network
setting every like usually if you want
the right protocol to be secure against
what folks like to work attackers and we
actually assume that network attackers
can agree it can do much more attic and
not only block messages they can also
replace the duplicate them and also
stuff of course you can ask heuristic
that in practice usually we the abstract
away from from this question just say
like look the attackers super powerful
because we don't know what how powerful
he actually is now but now if you if you
look at the contrast of this and
specifically I told you that we have
this palette and pot in the middle that
handles all broadcasts and the reason
why we do these actually def better
efficiency and now it's getting
interesting
so because he didn't want to trust this
London bond in the middle of the server
and the middle fond of the Mitty but if
you if your fingers around the middle
being the malicious network attacker
then family it's very easy to block
messages right
it's just don't follow it and like think
of I think last week I mentioned a
simple example of IRC server broadcast
messages to everybody else so basically
in this setting if you had a server you
can always claim or look I didn't walk
didn't send the message she's offline
whoops
um now so we're just stepping if you
only feel so yeah okay efficiency and
they're cool next okay now this is the
flow chart again that we've seen and now
the title of the slide says naive why
not if because this is actually not a
lot of truth I think I started this
explanation of the previous slide some
actually because I was confused on the
slides
yeah okay let's count communication
rounds and communication rounds are here
broadcasts so we need one protocols for
the key exchange desert desert this is a
symbol here right here okay then we need
one protocol to run the actual these
units and now I guess now is the crucial
part because we all need to like all the
peers now needs to increase on whether
the protocol has been disrupted
on
am i told you this example where you can
selectively disrupt messages from from
peers so to avoid this in the 90 favor
would needs another broadcast here just
to check that we all agree on whether
they're worse disruption or not because
as I as I explained to you earlier the
only thing you can do it you can look at
this on the out front of the protocol
and see if his own messages there but he
doesn't know if the message of the
others are there so to make sure that we
all agree whether there was disruption
or not we would need another broadcast
round here and this is the broadcast
that and then once we all know whether
there has been disruption or not we need
one more broadcast either to broadcast
signatures on the contract transaction
watch who revealed the key exchange
secrets depending on which way we go now
okay now in contra 4 + + so sorry
can you go back one step
yes so and if we look at this now if we
count the broadcast these are basically
four broadcasts and every run right no
matter which which way we go now what we
do instead in contra los + next is we
skip we want to avoid this broadcast at
the disrupted box here and how do we do
that next
by introducing another broadcast here
huh
so so far this doesn't make a lot of
sense right because we still have for
broadcast it currently replace one
broadcast by another firm crust the let
me explain you why this makes sense
next okay let me first tell you why what
we actually do so what we do here is it
like the first broadcast that we
introduce now is basically a commitment
cryptographic commitments to the T seen
inspector by with time interest the
roast of the that appears sent and the
TC net so we first sent a commitment
next and then we sent the actual
dissonant contents the actual rows so
why do we do this
the idea is basically it is that now we
get this following relationship now by
doing this we get the guarantee that if
there is a if there is one or the
serious message is disrupted then all of
the messages are disrupted and the other
way round
this basically means that now instead of
needing a broadcast route to to check if
to to track with the others if there has
been disruption what we what we now can
do instead is really just looking at our
own at all output so you look at all of
the look at the list of messages and see
if your own message is there and you
know if you're all the messages say then
all the other words and equally you know
if your own messages it's not there at
and also the other messages on
they're so yeah and the rest of the
slide was just formal stuff not
interesting here so now let's look at an
example go back please
yep so if now protocol would it's a run
so let's say we have a first run of the
protocol and now having boxes of for
prod costs and remember that the DC net
round is now in the third position right
because we first sent the key exchanged
and the second fingers commit whoa did
you see that vectors to the messages
then we sent the actual DC net measured
the third round this is what I mean when
I read TC and then in the end we heat
her to the intercept the signatures
around or of the revealed of key
exchange messages and now let's assume
like okay this first one is disrupted
next and remember the disruption happens
in the DC no transyl that somebody sent
in this unit round this round
is disrupted the round is disrupted
anyways what starts a second Tron and
would need another another four rounds
if you go back again sorry
so this is the this is the IE thing and
now next what we don't control plus plus
is if you actually want to type like
this runs and to reduce the number of
overalls
so now the idea is basically we run two
rounds of the first one and then we
already start a second one it's not
clear yet if people needed or not but in
case the first one is is disrupted then
we can just switch to the second run
which is the the example here right and
then maybe the the second one actually
is not disrupted and okay we have
started already at the retron just in
case and then okay but the second one
works run-through so we can just support
the third one this is how we pipeline
this and now look at this red line here
this is how the how the information flow
is basically from the from the first one
to the second one because the first one
can remember the first one was disrupted
right so after the after the fourth
message of the last message of the first
one only then we learned who is the
malicious party because this is where we
reveal the secrets and note now this can
see this from the red line now this is
exactly the point in time it's still so
it's still okay to exclude the malicious
guy no for the second one because now
the malicious guy that excluded the
first run counts dropped the second one
because we managed to exclude him from
the second run before me before we each
the DC thing for me to reach to DC
message face does this make sense he's
asked if this is okay make sense to me
great and and this is the reason why we
wanted to push the DC metro to the third
probe cast instead of the second so this
was the thing I've ever owned you on the
previous slides read the information we
run key exchange then already DC net and
then we need to check with the others if
disruption happens then the diziness
round
would be in the scene that message
within the second round but here what we
act what we here do is through this
commitments of DC net and then sending
that we see not only in the third round
he be moved to DC no to the third round
we make this interleaving of to here
possible yeah now if you if you count
the number of rounds that we have F
malicious users then we need four plus
twelve broadcaster ons and this is
better than previous work just for
original code travel which was just
often Efron's
so what's your yeah and that we can
every night doesn't vectors would
basically to set up today when June here
on the slide and compare this to the
previous protocol control fool and at
least in this setting plus plus it's
much much better control as you can see
under on the craft so yeah for example
for security a number of you point out
on the papers 5050 notes there we are
still below 10 seconds into something
and then crunch awful original coin
shuffle was like almost three minutes of
this sitting next yep next
okay and then just I think this is maybe
should have been called limitations of
coins on actually photos for this
audience fear puts you you're probably
aware that handling unequally inputs is
a like if for was a very bad idea right
because like if you had to a transaction
like it's like it's on the slides here
it and everybody could just every Excel
observer even control cell that pop
like the one point can go back so yeah
so if everybody looks at this
transaction can just sell that P and P
Prime belong together right there's no
there's no privacy if if we do my if
conjoined with unequal inputs and tempt
and we all know Adam has much better
suggestions to do this but this is still
obvious limitation of contracts okay and
also this is more subtle what we what we
also can't do in in current shuffle plus
plus is the following so actually I
don't want you to mix your money right
you want to also to pay with your money
so hope you could have tea idea to you
can or cannot do this you cannot and I
will tell you why the United payment in
the conjoint year like there's a pizza
restaurant but address our and he sent
Co point one Bitcoin to the pizza
restaurant and then she he sends the
remaining silver problem because back to
in prime which is his change address and
our like if you if you just think so
most server you need look at this
transaction I mean of course you can you
can see that zero point one is zero and
I belong together but you couldn't tell
whether they they both belong to a B or
C however the reason why it doesn't work
is small subtle namely next now look at
what would be the messages that we have
to send to the peer-to-peer mixing
protocol like in
the contrary just non-conscious applause
plastron we would just send the output
to us which is R and B prime here now
would basically have two messages in the
peer-to-peer problem mixing protocol one
for R and 1 for y Prime and now these
messages are not just a simple the T
addresses because he also needs society
amounts there right because like the
amounts are not implicit and more like
in the previous example where everybody
has one Bitcoin like team rounds are
nothing to laugh like a lot message said
need to be mixed but here they would
need to be mixed so basically since two
messages and one of the messages is to
pair our comma zero point one and the
reason why this doesn't work is now that
the zero point one is is a fixed message
it's nothing that you can discard and
then throw a new random one right just
doesn't work either because does that
matter what really matters is that the
output address is changed so it's like
the message is not not the zero point on
the messages or 0.1 if you next you
message or to zero point one because
Robert gave you many addresses yeah but
it's all think like a it is we had this
side topic right is our fresh no message
is actually necessary can we do mix so
it can be to fix messages and the reason
why the answer was no the reason was
that an annuity is problem so
functionally it your rights you can
trust like if the first the first one
the support
that you could vote it and then we start
with R 2 and C 1 but then it could be
that there is an attack anonymity
now I'm sorry can you repeat that in the
had a few slides with the under the
title side topic are fresh fresh message
just necessary right away very shortly
it's a contestant for example but the
message it's fresh is just one component
of the messages fixed ok but the attack
basically applies to two also messages
[Music]
you really need to loosen Lumet into
certain also how would you pay someone
[Music]
you typically only connect can you
repeat so typically you only get one
address when you have to pay someone so
yeah ok yeah this is what I like if I
write the paper I would call this an
engineering challenge and put the
despite yes of course then you need to
but the your I don't know what it was
saying is you write the practice to
solve the problem it's just that it's
kind of trouble but you need to
recipient support and this would be
another topic even if it would be
possible either like if you if you do a
conjure with 50 bodies then either you
ask the pizza restaurant so give you a
49ers resist which is art me but works
and well you have something like 32 and
pop in derivation and so on very like
[Music]
since the rest everyone would give you
one master
[Music]
almost a public kid and you can just
derive an arbitrary number of virtual
addresses from it
so just to reiterate on the problem here
is that when you expose your messages
then of course you don't expose the
between addresses but what you expose is
that you want to send 0.1 and 0.9 and
then what you could do with that is that
well I guess this descent failed because
the peers where were malicious though
I'm just going to send one Bitcoin in in
the failing ground but you know you
could you could assume honesty and and
if if honesty yep and then I mean it's
not very robust but you can nobody I see
what you're saying let me let me repeat
to make sure I get the right thing so
what you're saying is basically a be
optimistic I try to like the first run
try to do the pavement and then but if
this first run fails then go back to
simple mixing without paying yes
yeah this you're right this principle
would work it's a good question how
robust this is and practice but in
principle you could do this all right
thank you
okay and now like this is the final
words here on the slides I think so this
already like if if we are in a system
where we have confidential transactions
which was the cryptographic technique to
hide the amounts on deterrence actress
like the amounts are not on plane stolen
plane but are in
morphic comes in cryptographically once
then suddenly those mounts because there
are commitments these are not fixed
messages anymore those are this can be
rear-ended - physically so you can take
a commitment and like you can commit to
the same amount twice and the
commitments look totally independent of
each other then this problem with the
fixed message goes away and then you
suddenly can mix up a simultaneously and
also like and attentive protocol you use
when you shuffle which is full of work
and also you you of course get rid of
the previous problem that you can't mix
unequally most and you can also mix
equal amounts and suddenly mixing is so
much nicer and better see if you could
hide the amounts but I think this that I
have one more more theoretical and less
practical octet
you know what what does really
termination mean here termination means
that everyone signs but the not deliver
termination it termination is that
successful broadcast happens so now
there is a shoe with double spins yeah
right yeah we detect the double spins
and then we have to run the whole
protocol again yeah but if you are a
minor then everyone has to be online
until confirmation joy at the end around
yeah the problem is trusted you you
don't you don't figure it out so quickly
right so and
don't write essays I've shown you on the
slides basically the protocol is
finished as soon as you get the
signatures of the control message at the
concert elections from everybody else
then you have a signed contract then if
naively then you think like the protocol
is finished I just need to broadcast the
transaction to the network now and then
at once do but yeah like in reality
people could double spend maybe a minute
later or so not sure how realistic a
minute is if you're mining here's the
smartest way to be double spent here
would be that you divide the network
like one half of it knows about the
correct transaction the other half of it
doesn't know about the correct
transaction so the the the peers cannot
really agree if the protocol was
disrupted or not how do you like
everything this season I mean it's it's
I think it's a problem with every
control finger it so I mean if I if I
broadcast two transactions like two six
and six peers at the exact same time
then they are propagating on the network
in a way that that that the man who will
splits and then a minor has to come to
decide which one was actually the real
transaction right now I mean my
Christmas if you have seen this taken
wasabi or somewhere else I see double
spent possibly Cohen joins like maybe a
year ago I could not figure out what to
was that okay
I always wanted
in practice I mean like if you of course
you can do this attack but it's pretty
pointless for the attractor I don't know
it's just super annoying yeah it's like
you know other schemes those are working
in practice don't even and your denial
of service protection right Android this
this is like a new level of theoretical
attack so I it's an engineering
challenge as you would put it yeah I
mean it would at least say it's not the
end of the world but like even the even
if people do this attack actively you
can what you can do is wait for another
minute or so and like and if you have if
you haven't seen a conflicting
transaction four minutes
well okay and you can be like actually
the the peers can also then then we lay
the transactions right like a fault is
it's like if one of the piece of the
protocol sees a conflicting transaction
could relay it to the others basically
have proof that okay okay yes yeah
that's my point would there be but you
wouldn't see because the nodes don't
broadcast to you but but yeah you can
relay to the others and like if but it's
kind of running time perspective kinds
of annoying right now I told you okay
like you know 10 seconds I'll tell you
oh you need to wait another 20 seconds
just to make sure there's I mean if if
others really a transaction like that
conflicting transaction then would that
I mean you would have to trust the other
peers that they are not lying about the
conflicting turns oh no because they can
only the transaction those are theirs so
they would be the
the the the guys who are disrupting the
round so yeah never mind I think like I
think you could just assume that like if
this transaction exists and it's signed
it's already not okay guys okay so maybe
I'll ask a question if that's okay Tim
in the yep
well you can usually ask the speaker to
go back to you can pay depending on how
many malicious piers there are that's a
good question so basically which
basically means four rounds right and
you know you know the protocol protocol
needs four plus two F rounds if you have
F malicious users so you can already is
like using this number you could just
scale it across but the problem is that
this is entirely the right answer
because here when I say there are no
malicious uses that's also here means
that they are all produce ponds of right
so like this is also at some party turn
I need to decide when when somebody is
offline it's um
the time off and now inserting here
basically we don't need the time off
because you assume everybody